It can actually be a very smart move for financially confident people.
And there are different ways to borrow money.
You can borrow from a friend or family member if you're comfortable with that.
Many people also borrow from a bank, lines of credit, a credit card, a car loan, or a mortgage for a house.
There's also some loans available from the government like student loans.
Borrowing money can help you achieve financial and life goals.
But it's important to borrow wisely, manage your debt well and limit your borrowing to what you can afford.
You know your own financial situation best.
So set your own debt limits.
Don't let others set them for you.